aftercollege.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy | AfterCollege

Your privacy is our top concern. We are committed to making sure that your personally identifiable information is kept confidential when you use AfterCollege and that your contact information will not be shared with another User without your consent. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and that it is used specifically for purposes that are in-line with AfterCollege`s mission of helping you improve your career. However, despite our efforts to maintain the confidentiality and security of your account, no method of transmission over the Internet and no method of electronic storage is completely secure. Although, we make every effort to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Visitor Information**

AfterCollege aggregates visitor data to analyze user patterns and generate site statistics. Your individual information is kept confidential and only used as part of anonymous aggregate data that helps us improve AfterCollege. We may also use your visitor information to provide you with an enhanced personalized surfing experience.

**Individual Information**

When you sign up as a User of AfterCollege, we may require specific information from you, such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone, billing information, etc. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us and/or having such information displayed on AfterCollege or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, you should not become a User. We may use your contact information to make you aware of additional services that may be of interest to you, or to contact you regarding changes to our service or new releases. We may also ask you for your feedback, opinions, and preferences in order to provide you with better services

Alternately, you may sign up as a User of AfterCollege by creating your account using a third party social networking site, "SNS", (including, but not limited to, Facebook). If you decide to sign up, we will extract the publicly available personally identifiable information that you have provided to the SNS (such as your name, email address and other information you make publically available via the SNS) from the account you have with such SNS and use the information to create your account on AfterCollege. The specific information that we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS. You hereby consent to our access to and collection of personally identifiable information about you via such SNS. 

Once you become a User, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, professional experiences, and objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration to become a User is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself, be introduced to potential employers, and find new opportunities on AfterCollege. 

Certain information you provide to AfterCollege may reveal, or allow others to identify, your nationality, ethnic origin, religion or other aspects of your private life, and generally more about you. The supplying of all such information by you to AfterCollege, including all information deemed "sensitive" by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. Please be aware that in providing information to AfterCollege for the purposes of becoming a User, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and AfterCollege`s Terms of Service. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive.

Employers may use your personally identifiable information to contact you to learn more about your experience, skills, and interest. Employers may reach out to you directly if we have recommended you to employers either directly or thought a feed email. Generally, employers can view your profile and the content you provided when you are featured in our employer tools, an email feed, a resume book, by AfterCollege forwarding your profile to an employer and by employers browsing the AfterCollege network.

**Disclosure of Information**

While we may disclose your personally identifiable information to employers for career opportunities, we do not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third parties without your consent. If you submit your information through certain co-branded sites that have agreements with AfterCollege, your information becomes property of both AfterCollege (AfterCollege, Inc.) and the owners and/or operators of the co-branded site. AfterCollege may receive compensation through ads and/or affiliate links on our site. If you submit your information through these ads and/or affiliate links, your information becomes property of the owners and/or operators of those ads and/or affiliate links. AfterCollege is not responsible for the way these sites use your information, but we will do our best to ensure the confidentiality of your information.

You acknowledge, consent and agree that AfterCollege may access, preserve and disclose your account information and Content (a) if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with legal process; (ii) enforce the Terms of Service; (iii) respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third parties; (iv) respond to your requests for customer service; or (v) protect the rights, property or personal safety of AfterCollege, its users and the public; (b) to employers, (c) to business partners, (d) to third party contractors such as developers, support administrators, designers, data analyst, and technicians who operation and maintain AfterCollege, (e) to a third party entity in the event of an assignment, (f) to legal, financial, and other professional advisor and (g) to a buyer or successor in anticipation of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of AfterCollege`s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by AfterCollege about our users is among the assets transferred.

**Profiles and Resumes**

Your resume and/or profile becomes property of AfterCollege, Inc. once posted on our site or any other site owned or operated by AfterCollege. We will make your resume or profile available to employers.  However, in accordance with our Terms of Service, you may log on to your account and delete your profile from AfterCollege at any time.

Be aware that when applying to a specific job or opportunity, scholarship, registering for an event, you authorize AfterCollege to release your contact information to the employer who posted the opportunity.

**Discussion Forums**

AfterCollege may use discussion forums, blogs or other similar platforms to provide a more interactive experience to its users. Some of these tools may require you to register in order to use them. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal data. In almost all instances, we give you the option of maintaining your name and email private.

**Email Communications**

By signing up on AfterCollege or any site owned or operated by AfterCollege, you will receive emails with career-related and other relevant information. For example, if you specify that you are a job seeker, you will receive career digests with relevant information pertinent to your affiliations. We will provide you with the options to unsubscribe from mailings. You also understand and agree that AfterCollege may send certain service-related communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, and that these communications are considered part of AfterCollege membership and you will not be able to opt out of receiving them.

**Surveys and Email Feedback**

AfterCollege periodically conducts surveys that help us obtain feedback. Your answers and suggestions help us improve our service and allow us to develop new and innovative tools. Information submitted through surveys and via email becomes property of AfterCollege. We will preserve your privacy, but reserve the right to use your name and school or company affiliation for our success stories and testimonials. We will not release your contact information in these testimonials. If you would like to email us your feedback or success story but would like it to remain confidential, please express your intention clearly in your email.

**Children**

AfterCollege is not intended for children under 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

Children aged 13 or older should not submit any personally identifiable information without the permission of their parents or guardians. By using AfterCollege, you are representing that you are at least 18, or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents` permission to use our website, services or tools.

**California Users**

California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to AfterCollege at our email address in order to receive information on the categories of customer information that we shared and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information, please and email message to [info@aftercollege.com](mailto:info@aftercollege.com) with "Request for California Privacy Information" in the subject line and in the body of your message. AfterCollege will provide the requested information to your email address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California S.B. 27 "Shine the Light" law requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

AfterCollege is committed to helping you find a job, and to preserving your privacy in the process.

**Company Information**

Phone: 415-263-1300 (8 am to 5 pm PST)  
Toll-Free: 877-725-7721 (8 am to 5 pm PST)  
Fax: 415-651-8927  
Email: info@aftercollege.com

Mailing Address:  
AfterCollege, Inc.  
98 Battery Street, Suite 601  
San Francisco, CA 94111
